Guide to the Marilyn Skolnick Papers, 1952-2009 AIS.2001.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Southwestern Pennsylvania Commission/Southwestern Pennsylvania Regional Planning Commission, 1979-2005; III.
  Due to her interest in the Pennsylvania transportation cause, Marilyn Skolnick was involved in the SPRPC and participated in many of its committees; in particular, she served as a member of the Transportation Plan Policy Committee for the Long Range Transportation Plan. This series originally contained publications concerning SPC/SPRPC drafts and final reports regarding transportation improvement programs that were duplications of other documents or available elsewhere.
  This series is organized into three subseries, alphabetically, by committee.The material in this series date from 1979 to 2005.
  - Agendas, Memos, Minutes, Correspondence, 1979-2005; 1.
    The documents in this subseries date from 1979 to 2005 and are arranged chronologically by year.
    - 1979 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - 1982 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - 1990 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - 1990-1997 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - 1990-1999 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - 1992 (Box 56, Folder 9-10)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - 1992-1996 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - 1992-1998 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - 1992-1999 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - 1993 (Box 56, Folder 15-17)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - 1993-1998 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - 1994 (Box 56, Folder 20-22)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - 1994-1996 (Box 56, Folder 24-25)
    - 1994-2000 (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - 1995 (Box 56, Folder 27-28)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - 1995-1997 (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - 1995-1998 (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - 1996 (Box 57, Folder 1-2)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - 1996-2002 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - 1997 (Box 57, Folder 5-6)
    - 1998 (Box 57, Folder 7-10)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - 1999 (Box 57, Folder 12-19)
    - 1999-2001 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - 2000 (Box 57, Folder 21-23)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - 2001 (Box 57, Folder 25-31)
    - 2005 (Box 57, Folder 32)
    - undated (Box 57, Folder 33-36)
  - Committees, 1991-2002; 2.
    - Administrative Advisory Committee, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 37)
    - Airport System Planning Program Advisory Committee, 1997 (Box 57, Folder 38)
    - Bicycle and Pedestrian Advisory Group, 1994-1996 (Box 57, Folder 39)
    - Bicycle and Pedestrian Advisory Group, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 40)
    - Citizens Advisory Panel (CAP), 1993-1994 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Citizens Advisory Panel (CAP), 1994-1995 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Citizens Advisory Panel (CAP), 1995-1997 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Citizens Advisory Panel (CAP), 1997-1998 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Council Plan Policy Committee, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - CMAQ Evaluation Committee, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - CMAQ Evaluation Committee, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Environmental Issues Committee, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Environmental Issues Committee, 1996-1999 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Forecasting Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Forecasting Committee, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - ITS Steering Committee, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - ITS Steering Committee, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 13-14)
    - ITS Steering Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Innovative Finance Subcommittee, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Natural Resources Committee, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Public Participation Panel, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Public Participation Panel, 1995-1998 (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Public Participation Panel, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Public Participation Panel, 1999-2001 (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Public Participation Panel, 2000-2001 (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - Public Participation Panel, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Regional Policy Committee, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Regional Policy Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Regional Policy Committee, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 3-4)
    - Regional Policy Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Regional Policy Committee, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Regional Policy Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Sewage Facilities Task Force, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - State Transportation Commission, 1996 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Transportation Improvement Program (TIP), 1991-1994 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Transportation Improvement Program (TIP), 1993-1996 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Transportation Improvement Program (TIP), 1994 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Transportation Improvement Program (TIP), 1994-1995 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Transportation Improvement Program (TIP), 1994-1996 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Transportation Improvement Program (TIP), 1995 (Box 59, Folder 15-16)
    - Transportation Improvement Program (TIP), 1995-1998 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Transportation Improvement Program (TIP), 1995-1999 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Transportation Improvement Program (TIP), 1996 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Transportation Improvement Program (TIP), 1996-1999 (Box 59, Folder 20-21)
    - Transportation Improvement Program (TIP), 1996-2000 (Box 59, Folder 22-23)
    - Transportation Improvement Program (TIP), 1996-2001 (Box 59, Folder 24)
    - Transportation Improvement Program (TIP), 1997 (Box 59, Folder 25)
    - Transportation Improvement Program (TIP), 1997-2000 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Transportation Improvement Program (TIP), 1999-2004 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Transportation Improvement Program (TIP), 2000 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Transportation Improvement Program (TIP), 2000-2001 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Transit Committee, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Transit Operators Committee (TOC), 1994 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Transit Operators Committee (TOC), 1994-1995 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Transit Operators Committee (TOC), 1995 (Box 60, Folder 8-10)
    - Transit Operators Committee (TOC), 1995-1997 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Transit Operators Committee (TOC), 1997 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Transit Operators Committee (TOC), 1998-1999 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Transit Operators Committee (TOC), 1999 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Transit Operators Committee (TOC), 2000-2002 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Transit Operators Committee (TOC), 1999-2000 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Transportation Plan Policy Committee (TPPC), 1992 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Transportation Plan Policy Committee (TPPC), 1993 (Box 60, Folder 18-19)
    - Transportation Plan Policy Committee (TPPC), 1994 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Transportation Policy Committee (TPC), 1996 (Box 60, Folder 21-22)
    - Transportation Policy Committee (TPC), 1996 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Transportation Policy Committee (TPC), 1997 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Transportation Policy Committee (TPC), 1997-1998 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Transportation Policy Committee (TPC), 1998 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Transportation Technical Committee (TTC), 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Transportation Technical Committee (TTC), 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Transportation Technical Committee (TTC), 1994 (Box 61, Folder 7-9)
    - Transportation Technical Committee (TTC), 1994-1995 (Box 61, Folder 10-11)
    - Transportation Technical Committee (TTC), 1996 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Transportation Technical Committee (TTC), 1997 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Transportation Technical Committee (TTC), 1997-1998 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Transportation Technical Committee (TTC), 1998 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Transportation Technical Committee (TTC), 1999 (Box 61, Folder 16-18)
    - Transportation Technical Committee (TTC), 2000 (Box 62, Folder 1-3)
    - Transportation Technical Committee (TTC), 2000-2001 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Transportation Technical Committee (TTC), 2001 (Box 62, Folder 5-6)
    - VIP2 Steering Committee, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Newsclips, 1994-2001; 3.
    - September 1994-November 1994 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - June 1995-October 1995 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - September 1995-February 1996 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - December 1995-April 1996 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - February 1996-June 1996 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - February 1997-April 1997 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - September 1997-January 1998 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - January 1999-April 1999 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - July 1999-November 1999 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - July 2000-August 2000 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - January 2001-April 2001 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - April 2001-June 2001 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - June 2001-July 2001 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - July 2001-October 2001 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Projects, Studies, Conferences, 1988-2002; 4.
    - 2020 Vision, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - Air Quality Conformity Determination, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - Airport Corridor Service Development Plan, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - Allegheny County Railroad Corridor Study Final Report, 1991 (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - Annual Policy Conference, Organizational Assessment, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - Annual Policy Conference, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - Annual Policy Conference, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 28-29)
    - Annual Policy Conference, 2001 (Box 62, Folder 30-31)
    - Buhl Science Center, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 32)
    - Congestion Management System Analysis, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 33)
    - Crow's Run Letters of Opposition and Support, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 34)
    - Crow's Run Opposition, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Crow's Run Support, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Crow's Run Southern Beltway, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Cycle V Forecast, undated (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Discussion Group, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Highway Users Benefit, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Intelligent Transportation Systems, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Kochanowski, Robert -Memorandums and Comments, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Lawrenceville Development, 1996 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Long Range Plan, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Long Range Plan, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 11-13)
    - Long Range Plan, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Long Range Plan, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 15-16)
    - Major Investment Studies, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Major Metropolitan Transportation Investment, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous, 1996 (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Mon/Fayette, 1999-2000 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Pamphlet, A Region on the Move, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Park and Ride Study, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - PennDot State Transportation Commission Hearing, 1996 (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Pittsburgh Area Cycling Coalition, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - Pittsburgh Counties and Municipalities, 1996 (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - Planning Review, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - Plumbing for the Future, undated (Box 63, Folder 27)
    - Project Lists, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 28)
    - Proposed Major Projects, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 29)
    - Public Involvement Program, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 30)
    - Region Newsletter, 1995-1999 (Box 63, Folder 31)
    - Region Newsletter, 1997-2001 (Box 63, Folder 32)
    - Regional Air Cargo Strategies, undated (Box 63, Folder 33)
    - Regional Development Council Overall Economic Development, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 34)
    - Regional Development Council Resolutions, 1996 (Box 63, Folder 35)
    - Sierra Club Statements, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 36)
    - Strategic Transportation and Financing Conference, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 37)
    - Strategic Transportation and Financing Conference, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 38)
    - Studies, undated (Box 63, Folder 39)
    - South Portal Liberty Tubes Project, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 40)
    - Testimony for the Cargo Interchange, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 41)
    - SWPA, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 42)
    - SWPA, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 43)
    - Southern Beltway Feasibility Study, undated (Box 63, Folder 44)
    - Transportation Project Development Process Glossary, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 45)
    - Transit Project Summary, 1996 (Box 63, Folder 46)
    - Transportation Research Board, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 47)
    - Transportation Study, 1993-1999 (Box 63, Folder 48)
    - U.S. DOT, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - VIP2 Meeting, 1999 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Vision, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Walkability, undated (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Organizations, 1977-2002; IV.
  Marilyn Skolnick was involved with many organizations and it was this involvement that allowed her to push for change in the transportation spectrum early in her life. She did this through membership in the League of Women Voters in both Texas and Pennsylvania. During her participation in the League of Women Voters, Skolnick encouraged informed and active participation of Pennsylvania citizens. In the government realm, Marilyn used this organization to increase the understanding of major public policy.
  Not only was she Vice President and Director of the League of Women Voters, but Skolnick was also heavily involved in the Sierra Club in Allegheny County. The Sierra Club is America's oldest, largest, and most influential grassroots environmental organization. Marilyn served as Executive Director of the Allegheny County Chapter. Through memorandums, newsletters, conference notes, correspondence, agendas, minutes, organization literature, and studies, this series helps to provide insight into Skolnick's environmentalist background.
  This series originally contained some published books on environmental issues, as well as environmental statues and legislation that are readily available elsewhere.
  This series is organized into three subseries, arranged alphabetically, by organization. The material in this series date from 1977-2002.
  - Better Business Bureau, 1986-1998; 1.
    - Arbitration, 1986-1988 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Arbitration, 1993 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Arbitrator Training, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Arbitrator Training, undated (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Buick Motor Division Complaint, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Cochrain Pontiac Complaint, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Newsletter "the A Team", 1990 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Roster of Members, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Solutions, 1993-1998 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Solutions, 1996-1998 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - League of Women Voters, 1977-2002; 2.
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1985-1987 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Annual Reports, 1984-1993 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Attendance, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Global Issues, 1986-1987 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Issues, undated (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Legislation, undated (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Literature, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Mailings, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Meetings, 1985-1986 (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - Memoranda, 1986-1987 (Box 64, Folder 25-26)
    - Newsclippings, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - Newsletters, 1986-1987 (Box 64, Folder 28)
    - Policy, undated (Box 64, Folder 29)
    - Reports, 1988-1992 (Box 64, Folder 30)
    - Resources, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 31)
    - Resolution, undated (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Studies, 1977-1983 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Transportation, 1997-1999 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Transportation, undated (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - "National Voter", 1986-1988 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - "Pennsylvania Voter", 1986-1989 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - "Voter", 1986-1990 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - "Voter", 1996-2001 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - "Voter", 2002 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Sierra Club, 1981-2001; 3.
    - 2000 Election (Box 65, Folder 10-11)
    - Abortion Policy, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Action, 1990-1992 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Air Quality, 1991-1994 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Air Quality, 1993-1997 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Air Quality, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Air Quality, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Air Quality, 1996-1999 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Air Quality, 1997-1998 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Allegheny Group, 1991-1994 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Allegheny Group, 1997 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Allegheny Group Bylaws, 1988-1990 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Allegheny Group Campaign Questionnaire, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Allegheny Group Candidate Questionnaire, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 24-25)
    - Allegheny Group Citizens' Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Allegheny Group Meetings, undated (Box 65, Folder 27-28)
    - Ancient Forests, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - Annual Meeting, 1992-1998 (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - Annual Report, 1988-1989 (Box 65, Folder 31)
    - Annual Report, 1992-1993 (Box 65, Folder 32)
    - B & W Project, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 33)
    - Balloon Launches, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 34)
    - Billboards, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 35)
    - Board Members, 1986-1987 (Box 65, Folder 36)
    - Board Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 65, Folder 37)
    - Board Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 65, Folder 38)
    - Brownfields, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 39)
    - Centennial, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 40)
    - Chair National Contacts, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 41)
    - Chapter Testimony, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 42)
    - Citizen Power, 1997 (Box 65, Folder 43)
    - Clean Air, 1987-1988 (Box 65, Folder 44)
    - Clean Air Chair, 1989-1990 (Box 65, Folder 45)
    - Congressional Involvement, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 46)
    - Conservation, 1989-1990 (Box 65, Folder 47)
    - Conservation, 1994-2001 (Box 65, Folder 48)
    - Conservation, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 49)
    - Conservation, 1997-1999 (Box 65, Folder 50)
    - Conservation Committee, 1988-1990 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Conservation Policies, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Contracts, 1989-1990 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 7-8)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1998 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 13-14)
    - Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 66, Folder 16-17)
    - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 66, Folder 18-22)
    - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 23-24)
    - Department of Environmental Protection, 1996 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Dolphin Campaign, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Education, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Educational Project, undated (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - Emissions, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - Environmental Enforcement, 1996-1997 (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - Environmental Quality Board, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Environmental Quality Board, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Environmental Scorecard, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 33)
    - Environmental Spotlight, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 34)
    - EXCOM, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 35)
    - EXCOM, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 36)
    - EXCOM, 1992-1998 (Box 66, Folder 37)
    - EXCOM, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 38)
    - EXCOM, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 39)
    - EXCOM, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 40)
    - EXCOM, 1998-1999 (Box 66, Folder 41)
    - EXCOM, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 42)
    - EXCOM, 2001 (Box 66, Folder 43)
    - EXCOM, undated (Box 66, Folder 44)
    - EXCOM Agenda, 1988-1989 (Box 66, Folder 45)
    - EXCOM Elections, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 46)
    - Expense Forms, undated (Box 66, Folder 47)
    - Factory Farm Pollution, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 48)
    - Financials, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 49)
    - Financials, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 50)
    - Financials, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 51)
    - Financials, 1997-1998 (Box 66, Folder 52)
    - Financials, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 53)
    - Forests, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 54)
    - Frazier Township Mall, 1991-1992 (Box 66, Folder 55)
    - Global Warming, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 56)
    - Grassroots Information System, undated (Box 66, Folder 57)
    - Grassroots Sierra, 1989-1990 (Box 66, Folder 58)
    - Grassroots Sierra, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 59)
    - Growth Management, 1995-2000 (Box 66, Folder 60)
    - Growth Management, undated (Box 66, Folder 61)
    - Group Chairs Conference, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 62)
    - Gypsy Moth Management, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 63)
    - Harrisburg, 2001 (Box 66, Folder 64)
    - Home Rule Charter, 1996-1998 (Box 66, Folder 65)
    - Home Rule Charter, 1997 (Box 66, Folder 66)
    - IRRC, undated (Box 66, Folder 67)
    - Issues and Organizing, 1997 (Box 66, Folder 68)
    - Issue Policy, undated (Box 66, Folder 69)
    - Land Files, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 70)
    - Land Use, 1992-2000 (Box 66, Folder 71)
    - Lawsuit, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 72)
    - League of Women Voters, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Legislative Action, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Literature List, 1989-1990 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Long Range Plan, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Map, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Marshall Township, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Mediation, 1985 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Media Training Manual, undated (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Membership, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Membership, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Membership, 1999 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Membergram, 1991-1992 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Memorandum, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Mon/Fayette, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - National Board Meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - National Conservation Campaign, 1990-1991 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - National Conservation Campaign, 1991-1992 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - National Conservation Reviews, undated (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - National Fundraising, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - National Legal Defense, 1988 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - National Literature List, undated (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - National News Report, 1988-1989 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - National Population Report, 1987-1988 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - National Testimony, 1985-1990 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - National Transportation, 1988-1989 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - National Transportation Policy Hearing, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - National Sustainable Communities Committee, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - News, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 29)
    - Newsclippings, 1997 (Box 67, Folder 30)
    - Newsletters, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 31)
    - Newsletters, 1986-1991 (Box 67, Folder 32)
    - Newsletters, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 33)
    - Newsletters, 1996-1999 (Box 67, Folder 34)
    - Newsletters, Hazardous Waste, 1988 (Box 67, Folder 35)
    - Northeast Office, undated (Box 67, Folder 36)
    - Notes, Hayes, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 37)
    - Ohio Sustainable Transportation, undated (Box 67, Folder 38)
    - Outings, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 39)
    - Pamphlets, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 40)
    - Pest Management, 1988 (Box 67, Folder 41)
    - Policy, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 42)
    - Policy, undated (Box 67, Folder 43)
    - Political Committee, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 44)
    - Political Information Packet, 1989-1990 (Box 67, Folder 45)
    - Pollution Activist, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 46)
    - Population, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 47)
    - Project Oversight Committee, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 48)
    - Public Lands, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 49)
    - Public Lands, 1989-1992 (Box 67, Folder 50)
    - Public Lands Activists, 1988-1989 (Box 67, Folder 51)
    - Public Testimony, undated (Box 67, Folder 52)
    - Publications, 1996-1997 (Box 67, Folder 53)
    - Publications, 1997 (Box 67, Folder 54)
    - Reduction News, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 55)
    - Resolutions, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 56)
    - Resolutions, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 57)
    - Rio, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 58)
    - SCOPE, 1988 (Box 67, Folder 59)
    - SCOPE, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 60)
    - SCOPE, 1989-1991 (Box 67, Folder 61)
    - SCOPE, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 62)
    - SCOPE Action, 1989-1990 (Box 67, Folder 63)
    - SCOPE Committee, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 64)
    - SCOPE Election Material, 1985-1988 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - SCOPE League of Conservation Voters, 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - SCOPE Materials, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - SCOPE Material, undated (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - SCOPE Rules, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 5)